Guide to the Lee P. Brown Papers, 1954-2013 MS 509
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series XI: Houston Mayor, 1997-2004, 213482
  - Subseries D: Speeches, 230937
    - Denver Harbor Multi-Service Center, 1999-09-25; 255389 (Box 60, Folder 140)
    - Chinese Community 50th Anniversary National Day Celebration, 1999-09-26; 255390 (Box 60, Folder 141)
    - Mayor's Victory Lane Brunch, 1999-09-26; 255391 (Box 60, Folder 142)
    - Field Emergency Operations Center Unvieling Press Conference, 1999-09-27; 255392 (Box 60, Folder 143)
    - Mervyn's California Community Closet Press Conference, 1999-09-27; 255393 (Box 60, Folder 144)
    - Reliant Energy Power of Houston Press Conference, 1999-09-27; 255394 (Box 60, Folder 145)
    - Clear Lake Area Economic Development, 1999-09-28; 255395 (Box 60, Folder 146)
    - Mayor's Teacher's Day Excellency Awards, 1999-09-28; 255396 (Box 60, Folder 147)
    - Greater SW Chamber of Commerce Law Enforcement Day, 1999-09-30; 255397 (Box 60, Folder 148)
    - Houston Annenberg Challenge Grant, 1999-09-30; 255398 (Box 60, Folder 149)
    - Texas Printing Ribbon Cutting Ceremony, 1999-09-30; 255963 (Box 60, Folder 150)
    - Women Business Owners Public Policy Meeting, 1999-09-30; 256194 (Box 60, Folder 151)
    - VIP Reception Honoring Mayor Brown, 1999-10-01; 256195 (Box 60, Folder 152)
    - Youthfest '99 Conference and Rally, 1999-10-01; 256196 (Box 60, Folder 153)
    - Inauguration of Joel Osteen as Pastor of Lakewood Church, 1999-10-03; 256197 (Box 60, Folder 154)
    - GHP Board of Directors Meeting Brief/Houston Challenge 2000, 1999-10-05; 256198 (Box 60, Folder 155)
    - Greenspoint Business Association Breakfast Meeting, 1999-10-05; 256199 (Box 60, Folder 156)
    - Houston Small Business Summit Opening, 1999-10-05; 256200 (Box 60, Folder 157)
    - AME Texas Annual Conference, 1999-10-06; 256201 (Box 60, Folder 158)
    - Combined Meeting of Hispanic and Asian Anti-Crime Advisory Boards, 1999-10-11; 256202 (Box 60, Folder 159)
    - Houston Metropolitan Baptist Ministers Meeting, 1999-10-11; 257142 (Box 60, Folder 160)
    - Pinnacle Awards, 1999-10-12; 257646 (Box 60, Folder 161)
    - Second Annual Brownfields Redevelopment Conference Workshop, 1999-10-12; 257647 (Box 60, Folder 162)
    - David Ben Gurion Award Dinner, 1999-10-13; 257648 (Box 60, Folder 163)
    - Joint Library with Harris County Press Conference, 1999-10-13; 257649 (Box 60, Folder 164)
    - Environmental Service Center Grand Opening, 1999-10-14; 257650 (Box 60, Folder 165)
    - Houston "Call to Leadership" Reception, 1999-10-14; 257651 (Box 60, Folder 166)
    - Mayor's Millenium Makers Reception and Photo Unveiling, 1999-10-14; 257652 (Box 60, Folder 167)
    - NFL Rally/Party on the Plaza, 1999-10-14; 257653 (Box 60, Folder 168)
    - Texas-Mexico Bar Association Meeting, 1999-10-14; 257654 (Box 60, Folder 169)
    - Beauty Pageant Winners Visiting Houston, 1999-10-15; 257655 (Box 60, Folder 170)
    - Houston Mortgage Brokers Association, 1999-10-18; 257656 (Box 60, Folder 171)
    - International Business Conference, 1999-10-18; 257657 (Box 60, Folder 172)
    - Sunnyside-South Park Neighborhood Press Conference, 1999-10-18; 257658 (Box 60, Folder 173)
    - Greater Houston Business Procurement Forum, 1999-10-19; 257659 (Box 60, Folder 174)
    - Houston Restaurant Association, 1999-10-19; 257660 (Box 60, Folder 175)
    - Mayor's Summit for Women Sponsor Reception, 1999-10-19; 257661 (Box 60, Folder 176)
    - Adrian Garcia - After-Council Presentation, 1999-10-20; 257662 (Box 60, Folder 177)
    - GHP Colombia Trade Seminar, 1999-10-20; 257663 (Box 60, Folder 178)
    - Blood Center Press Conference, 1999-10-21; 257664 (Box 60, Folder 179)
    - Fire Department ECG Machine Press Conference, 1999-10-21; 257665 (Box 60, Folder 180)
    - Mayor Brown Speaking Points for Arena Endorsement, 1999-10-21; 257666 (Box 60, Folder 181)
    - Tejas Breakfast Club Meeting, 1999-10-21; 257667 (Box 60, Folder 182)
    - Debra Duncan Live Interview, 1999-10-22; 257668 (Box 60, Folder 183)
    - Drug Free Workplace Week, 1999-10-22; 257669 (Box 60, Folder 184)
    - Harrisburg and Sunset Rails-to-Trails Groundbreaking, 1999-10-22; 257670 (Box 60, Folder 185)
    - Consular Forum Gala, 1999-10-23; 257671 (Box 60, Folder 186)
    - Power of Houston Event, 1999-10-23; 257672 (Box 60, Folder 187)
    - Stimley-Blueridge Library Dedication/Ribbon Cutting, 1999-10-23; 257673 (Box 60, Folder 188)
    - Houston Challenge 2000 Reception, 1999-10-24; 257674 (Box 60, Folder 189)
    - Illegal Dumping Week, 1999-10-25; 257675 (Box 60, Folder 190)
    - Mayor's Proud Partners Awards Luncheon, 1999-10-25; 257676 (Box 60, Folder 191)
    - Mayor Brown Remarks Enron Field, 1999-10-26; 257677 (Box 60, Folder 192)
    - Senator Rodney Ellis Fundraiser, 1999-10-26; 257823 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Mayor's Reception Honoring Top 50 Women-Business Owners, 1999-10-27; 257824 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Council Member Felix Fraga's 70th Birthday, 1999-10-28; 257827 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - HFD Dispatch Review Press Conference, 1999-10-28; 257825 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Reception for Commissioner Yvonne Gates of Law Vegas, 1999-10-28; 257828 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Texas Minority Counsel Program Conference, 1999-10-28; 257826 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Arena Press Conference, 1999-10-29; 257830 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Houston 2012 Committee Reception, 1999-10-29; 257898 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Houston Realty Breakfast Club, 1999-10-29; 257829 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - KCOH Radio Interview, 1999-10-29; 257831 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - National Congress for Community Economic Development, 1999-10-29; 257832 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Zhejiang Province Delegation Photo Op, 1999-10-29; 257897 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Asian American Community Leadership Reception, 1999-10-31; 257899 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - GHP Luncheon Honoring Don J. Wang, 1999-11-03; 257900 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - International Relations and Trade Development Mission Briefing, 1999-11-04; 258009 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Southwest Airlines Check Presentation, 1999-11-04; 258286 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Hispanic Contractor's Association, 1999-11-05; 258287 (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - United Negro College Fund Black Tie Gala, 1999-11-05; 258288 (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - Aga Khan Foundation Partnership Walk, 1999-11-07; 258289 (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Kase Lawal Reception, 1999-11-08; 258290 (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - Mayor's Summit on Women, 1999-11-08; 258291 (Box 61, Folder 21)
    - After-Council Presentation - Monique McGilbra, 1999-11-09; 258292 (Box 61, Folder 22)
    - Associated Builders and Contractors Lunch, 1999-11-09; 258293 (Box 61, Folder 23)
    - Continental Airlines Ceremony, 1999-11-30; 258294 (Box 61, Folder 24)
    - Council Member Jean Kelley's Reception, 1999-11-30; 258295 (Box 61, Folder 25)
    - River Oaks Women's Breakfast Club Meeting, 1999-11-30; 258296 (Box 61, Folder 26)
    - African Trip Press Conference, 1999-12-01; 258297 (Box 61, Folder 27)
    - World AIDS Day Press Conference, 1999-12-01; 258298 (Box 61, Folder 28)
    - Fire Fighters Christmas Party, 1999-12-02; 258299 (Box 61, Folder 29)
    - Groundbreaking Ceremony for New Holiday Inn Express, 1999-12-02; 259546 (Box 61, Folder 30)
    - Seven Acres Jewish Geriatric Center, 1999-12-03; 259959 (Box 61, Folder 31)
    - Full Gospel Businesswoman's Fellowship, 1999-12-04; 259960 (Box 61, Folder 32)
    - Mayor's Official Downtown Holiday Celebration, 1999-12-04; 259961 (Box 61, Folder 33)
    - United Negro College Fund Taping, 1999-12-04; 259962 (Box 61, Folder 34)
    - University of Houston College of Education Commencement, 1999-12-04; 259963 (Box 61, Folder 35)
    - Mt. Canaan Missionary Baptist Church, 1999-12-05; 259964 (Box 61, Folder 36)
    - Access Mexico Trade Conference, 1999-12-06; 259965 (Box 61, Folder 37)
    - Groundbreaking for a Brand New Houston, 1999-12-06; 259966 (Box 61, Folder 38)
    - Helen Chang Breakfast, 1999-12-06; 259967 (Box 61, Folder 39)
    - South Asian American Political Action Committee, 1999-12-06; 259968 (Box 61, Folder 40)
    - Hobby Center Mural Project Unveiling, 1999-12-07; 259969 (Box 61, Folder 41)
    - HPD Storefront Opening, 1999-12-07; 259970 (Box 61, Folder 42)
    - Project Exile Press Conference, 1999-12-07; 259971 (Box 61, Folder 43)
    - Cleaning the Air Press Conference, 1999-12-08; 259972 (Box 61, Folder 44)
    - HGAC Clean Air Conference, 1999-12-08; 259973 (Box 61, Folder 45)
    - Memorial Herman Jingle Bell Run and Walk, 1999-12-08; 259974 (Box 61, Folder 46)
    - Big Brothers/Big Sisters of Houston Gala, 1999-12-09; 259975 (Box 61, Folder 47)
    - Mayor's 2nd Annual Ministers Holiday Breakfast, 1999-12-11; 259976 (Box 61, Folder 48)
    - Mayor's Youth Holiday Celebration, 1999-12-11; 259977 (Box 61, Folder 49)
    - St. Stephen Baptist Church, 1999-12-12; 259978 (Box 61, Folder 50)
    - Houston 2000 Transportation Plan, 1999-12-13; 259979 (Box 61, Folder 51)
    - Houston Transportation 2000 Steering Committee Meeting, 1999-12-13; 259980 (Box 61, Folder 52)
    - 21st Century Technology and Economic Development, 1999-12-14; 259981 (Box 61, Folder 53)
    - Affirmative Action Advisory Commission, 1999-12-14; 259982 (Box 61, Folder 54)
    - Mayor's Mentor Appreciation Breakfast, 1999-12-14; 259983 (Box 61, Folder 55)
    - Fleet Services Council Press Conference, 1999-12-15; 259984 (Box 61, Folder 56)
    - National Summit on Africa Police Forum, 1999-12-16; 259985 (Box 61, Folder 57)
    - Northline Park Store Front Opening Ceremony, 1999-12-16; 259986 (Box 61, Folder 58)
    - Holiday Greeting Audio Taping, 1999-12-17; 259987 (Box 61, Folder 59)
    - Outgoing Council Members Luncheon, 1999-12-17; 259988 (Box 61, Folder 60)
    - Venezuelan Mudslide Relief Press Conference, 1999-12-29; 259989 (Box 61, Folder 61)
    - Y2K Speaking Points, 1999-12; 259990 (Box 61, Folder 62)
    - Campaign Event, 1999; 259991 (Box 61, Folder 63)
    - Children, 1999; 259992 (Box 61, Folder 64)
    - Houston Vignettes with Mayor Brown, 1999; 259993 (Box 61, Folder 65)
    - Neighborhood Oriented Government, 1999; 259994 (Box 61, Folder 66)
    - Emergency Management, ca. 1999; 259995 (Box 61, Folder 67)
    - Ways to Improve Human Infrastructure, ca. 1999; 259996 (Box 61, Folder 68)
    - Take It to the Bridge, 2000-01-02; 259997 (Box 61, Folder 69)
    - Inaugural Address, 2000-01-03; 259998 (Box 61, Folder 70)
    - Black Go Texan Gala, 2000-01-29; 259999 (Box 61, Folder 71)
    - State of the City Address Research, 2000-01; 260000 (Box 61, Folder 72)
    - Don K. Clark Retirement, 2000-02-03; 260001 (Box 61, Folder 73)
    - UH-Clear Lake's 25th Anniversary Celebration, 2000-02-03; 260002 (Box 61, Folder 74)
    - Black History Month Festival, 2000-02-05; 260003 (Box 61, Folder 75)
    - Mayor's Night In at City Hall, 2000-02-10; 260004 (Box 61, Folder 76)
    - Police Pension Press Conference, 2000-02-10; 260005 (Box 61, Folder 77)
    - Houston Police Activities League - Black History Month, 2000-02-11; 260006 (Box 61, Folder 78)
    - Third Ward Multi Service Center Groundbreaking, 2000-02-14; 260007 (Box 61, Folder 79)
    - Eulogy for Robert "Bob" Lamb, Jr., 2000-02-17; 260008 (Box 61, Folder 80)
    - Firefighters Memorial Service, 2000-02-18; 260009 (Box 61, Folder 81)
    - Our Mother of Mercy Black History Awareness Month, 2000-02-21; 260010 (Box 61, Folder 82)
    - Recent Appointments/Promotions, 2000-02-22; 260011 (Box 61, Folder 83)
    - Rush Hour Traffic Control Press Conference, 2000-02-22; 260012 (Box 61, Folder 84)
    - Prayer and Memorial Service, 2000-02-23; 260013 (Box 61, Folder 85)
    - Mayor's Town Hall Prepatory Meeting, 2000-02-24; 260014 (Box 61, Folder 86)
    - Grand Opening of Twelve Canfield Place Apartments, 2000-02-25; 260015 (Box 61, Folder 87)
    - International Brotherhood for Electrical Workers Union, 2000-02-26; 260016 (Box 61, Folder 88)
    - Day of Honor 2000 Project, 2000-02-27; 260017 (Box 61, Folder 89)
    - United Orthodox Synagogue of Houston, 2000-02-27; 260018 (Box 61, Folder 90)
    - Funday in the Park Kick-off, 2000-03-02; 260019 (Box 61, Folder 91)
    - Town Hall Meeting Southwest Houston and Alief, 2000-03-02; 260020 (Box 61, Folder 92)
    - Finance Working Group Meeting, 2000-03-06; 260021 (Box 61, Folder 93)
    - Clean Air Testimony before Texas Senate Natural Resources Committee, 2000-03-07; 260022 (Box 61, Folder 94)
    - Sheraton Suites Houston by the Galleria, 2000-03-08; 260023 (Box 61, Folder 95)
    - Harris Country NFL/Rodeo Stadium Groundbreaking, 2000-03-09; 260024 (Box 61, Folder 96)
    - "How Media Images Correspond and Affect Reality: The Impact the Media Has on Our Committees", 2000-03-10; 260025 (Box 61, Folder 97)
    - 2000 U.S. Savings Bond Campaign, 2000-03-14; 260026 (Box 61, Folder 98)
    - READ Commission, 2000-03-14; 260027 (Box 61, Folder 99)
    - Arabia Shrine Temple Circus, 2000-03-21; 260028 (Box 61, Folder 100)
    - Census Announcement, 2000-03-22; 260029 (Box 61, Folder 101)
    - Miller Outdoor Theater Season Opening, 2000-03-22; 260030 (Box 61, Folder 102)
    - Thank You Reception Honoring African Cab Drivers, 2000-03-23; 260031 (Box 61, Folder 103)
    - Houston Citizens Chamber of Commerce, 2000-03-24; 260032 (Box 61, Folder 104)
    - The Audrey Jones Beck Building Opening, 2000-03-25; 260033 (Box 61, Folder 105)
    - Consulate of Australia - Baker Institute, 2000-03-26; 260034 (Box 61, Folder 106)
    - Houston Symphony - Dr. Charles Floyd, 2000-03-27; 260035 (Box 61, Folder 107)
    - Consular Corps and International Community of Houston, 2000-03-28; 260036 (Box 61, Folder 108)
    - Greater Houston Partnership, the City of Houston, and the Houston - Galveston Area Council, 2000-03-28; 260037 (Box 61, Folder 109)
    - Carrillo Elementary School, 2000-03-30; 260038 (Box 61, Folder 110)
    - Enron Field Ribbon Cutting, 2000-03-30; 260039 (Box 61, Folder 111)
    - Mayor's Service Award Luncheon, 2000-04-03; 260040 (Box 61, Folder 112)
    - Enron Field Opening Celebration, 2000-04-14; 260041 (Box 61, Folder 113)
    - Enron Field Workers and Family Appreciation Day, 2000-04-15; 260042 (Box 61, Folder 114)
    - Honoring Mayor Bo Xi Lai of Dalian China, 2000-04-06; 260043 (Box 61, Folder 115)
    - Dalian/Houston Business Promotion Conference, 2000-04-07; 260044 (Box 61, Folder 116)
    - African American Leadership Summit, 2000-04-08; 260045 (Box 61, Folder 117)
    - Crusade for Christ, 2000-04-08; 260046 (Box 61, Folder 118)
    - Keep 5 Alive, 2000-04-08; 260047 (Box 61, Folder 119)
    - Rally for Constable Chambers, 2000-04-08; 260048 (Box 61, Folder 120)
    - Lee Family Association Spring Banquet, 2000-04-09; 260318 (Box 61, Folder 121)
    - 2000 Prudential Spirit of Community Awards, 2000-04-10; 260320 (Box 61, Folder 122)
    - Semmes Park in Fifth Ward, 2000-04-10; 260322 (Box 61, Folder 123)
    - Mayor Sevland of Stavanger, 2000-04-11; 260336 (Box 61, Folder 124)
    - Census 2000 Pep Rally, 2000-04-12 (Box 61, Folder 125)
    - Stavanger Days in Texas, 2000-04-12; 260351 (Box 61, Folder 126)
    - Houston International Festival, 2000-04-14; 260352 (Box 61, Folder 127)
    - International Business Expo, 2000-04-14; 260353 (Box 61, Folder 128)
    - Clean Air Press Conference, 2000-04-17; 260354 (Box 61, Folder 129)
    - Citizens Review Committee, 2000-04-17; 260356 (Box 61, Folder 130)
    - Strategic Transporation Plan Steering Committee, 2000-04-17; 260358 (Box 61, Folder 131)
    - PANDA Press Conference, 2000-04-18; 260370 (Box 61, Folder 132)
    - Special Fiscal Affairs and Management Initiatives Committee, 2000-04-18; 260373 (Box 61, Folder 133)
    - Town Hall Meeting for Greater Hobby/Southeast Houston, 2000-04-18; 260376 (Box 61, Folder 134)
    - Mayor's Prayer Breakfast, 2000-04-19; 260377 (Box 61, Folder 135)
    - Thunderbears City-Wide Season Kickoff, 2000-04-20; 260379 (Box 61, Folder 136)
    - Greater Houston Partnership, 2000-04-25; 260381 (Box 61, Folder 137)
    - Honoring Small City Mayors, 2000-04-25; 260582 (Box 61, Folder 138)
    - Constable Ruben Davis Fundraiser, 2000-04-26; 260585 (Box 61, Folder 139)
    - Texas Department of Transportation Commission, 2000-04-27; 260595 (Box 61, Folder 140)
    - TSU Inaugural Ceremony for Dr. Priscilla Slade, 2000-04-27; 260599 (Box 61, Folder 141)
    - Bicycle Month Press Conference, 2000-05-01; 260600 (Box 61, Folder 142)
    - Senator Slade Gordon, 2000-05-01; 260602 (Box 61, Folder 143)
    - City of Houston Public Service Recognition Week Essay Contest, 2000-05-02; 260603 (Box 61, Folder 144)
    - Greater Houston Convention and Visitors Bureau Membership Committee, 2000-05-02; 260605 (Box 61, Folder 145)
    - Annual National Day of Prayer, 2000-05-04; 260606 (Box 61, Folder 146)
    - Garden Villas United Methodist Church, 2000-05-04; 260607 (Box 61, Folder 147)
    - Hobby Center for the Performing Arts, 2000-05-04; 260608 (Box 61, Folder 148)
    - Water Festival, 2000-05-05; 260609 (Box 61, Folder 149)
    - Asian/Pacific American Heritage Association, 2000-05-07; 260610 (Box 61, Folder 150)
    - South Union Church of Christ, 2000-05-07; 260626 (Box 61, Folder 151)
    - Houston Grand Opera America Conference, 2000-05-08; 260627 (Box 61, Folder 152)
    - National Tourism Week, 2000-05-08; 260629 (Box 61, Folder 153)
    - Morgan Kendal Homes Ribbon Cutting, 2000-05-09; 260632 (Box 61, Folder 154)
    - Prime Minister of Jamaica, 2000-05-10; 260634 (Box 61, Folder 155)
    - Football Bowl Game Press Conference, 2000-05-11; 260635 (Box 61, Folder 156)
    - Super Neighborhood Council, 2000-05-11; 260637 (Box 61, Folder 157)
    - Youth Poster Contest, 2000-05-11; 260639 (Box 61, Folder 158)
    - USOC Media Summit, 2000-05-12; 260640 (Box 61, Folder 159)
    - Mobile City Hall Unveiling, 2000-05-13; 260642 (Box 61, Folder 160)
    - Fundraiser for Senator David Cain, 2000-05-15; 260643 (Box 61, Folder 161)
    - Mayor's Women Conference, 2000-05-15; 260645 (Box 61, Folder 162)
    - Weightless Wonder Press Dedication, 2000-05-15; 260646 (Box 61, Folder 163)
    - Automated External Defibrillator Press Conference, 2000-05-16; 260647 (Box 61, Folder 164)
    - Houston Airport System and Beijing Capital International Airport Agreement, 2000-05-16; 260648 (Box 61, Folder 165)
    - The Imani School, 2000-05-16; 260649 (Box 61, Folder 166)
    - Reception for Rep. Ron Wilson, 2000-05-16; 260650 (Box 61, Folder 167)
    - Dr. Joe Ratliff's 30th Anniversary Celebration, 2000-05-17; 260656 (Box 61, Folder 168)
    - National Police Week Awards Ceremony, 2000-05-17; 260658 (Box 61, Folder 169)
    - Japan-America Society Annual Membership Meeting, 2000-05-18; 260659 (Box 61, Folder 170)
    - May Executive Forum, 2000-05-18; 260661 (Box 61, Folder 171)
    - Millenium Mayorthon, 2000-05-18; 260663 (Box 61, Folder 172)
    - Texaco Havoline Grand Prix Kickoff, 2000-05-18; 260664 (Box 61, Folder 173)
    - 2001 Budget, 2000-05-19; 260665 (Box 61, Folder 174)
    - E.O. Smith Middle School, 2000-05-19; 260666 (Box 61, Folder 175)
    - HPD Memorial Service, 2000-05-19; 260667 (Box 61, Folder 176)
    - Tuttle Library Re-Opening, 2000-05-23; 260668 (Box 61, Folder 177)
    - Mayor's Women in Technology Conference, 2000-05-24; 260669 (Box 61, Folder 178)
    - Police Activities League Photo-Op, 2000-05-25; 260670 (Box 61, Folder 179)
    - Energy Summit, 2000-05-26; 260671 (Box 61, Folder 180)
    - Fellows of Harvard University, 2000-05-26; 260808 (Box 61, Folder 181)
    - Transporation Planning Conference, 2000-05-31; 260809 (Box 61, Folder 182)
    - Corder Place Apartments, 2000-06-01; 260810 (Box 61, Folder 183)
    - Hard Rock Cafe at Bayou Palace Grand Opening, 2000-06-01; 260811 (Box 61, Folder 184)
    - Jazz Festival/Education Press Conference, 2000-06-01; 260812 (Box 61, Folder 185)
    - People to People Student Ambassadors, 2000-06-01; 260813 (Box 61, Folder 186)
    - YMCA Ribbon Cutting Ceremony, 2000-06-02; 260814 (Box 61, Folder 187)
    - Gay and Lesbian Victory Fund, 2000-06-03; 260815 (Box 61, Folder 188)
    - World Trade Gala, 2000-06-03; 260816 (Box 61, Folder 189)
    - eGovernment Conference, 2000-06-05; 260817 (Box 61, Folder 190)
    - David Fisher Reception, 2000-06-07; 260818 (Box 61, Folder 191)
    - Reliant Energy Power of Freedom, 2000-06-07; 260819 (Box 61, Folder 192)
    - 225th Birthday of the U.S. Army, 2000-06-14; 260820 (Box 61, Folder 193)
    - Hobby Central Concourse Groundbreaking, 2000-06-15; 260821 (Box 61, Folder 194)
    - Houston Urban League Scholarships, 2000-06-15; 260822 (Box 61, Folder 195)
    - NAACP Membership Drive Campaign, 2000-06-15; 260823 (Box 61, Folder 196)
    - Society for the Performing Arts, 2000-06-15; 260824 (Box 61, Folder 197)
    - Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars, 2000-06-20; 260825 (Box 61, Folder 198)
    - Hispanic Media Professionals, 2000-06-21; 260826 (Box 61, Folder 199)
    - National Congress of Christian Education, 2000-06-21; 260827 (Box 61, Folder 200)
    - Denny's Classic Diner Grand Opening, 2000-06-22; 260828 (Box 61, Folder 201)
    - Designation of Super Neighborhood, 2000-06-22; 260829 (Box 61, Folder 202)
    - HFD Commencement, 2000-06-22; 260830 (Box 61, Folder 203)
    - Pathfinders Historical Sites Tour, 2000-06-22; 260831 (Box 61, Folder 204)
    - Greater St. Matthew Baptist Church Groundbreaking, 2000-06-25; 260832 (Box 61, Folder 205)
    - Democrat and Republic Precinct Judges Reception, 2000-06-27; 260833 (Box 61, Folder 206)
    - Downtown Street Construction Update, 2000-06-28; 260834 (Box 61, Folder 207)
    - Junior Achievement, 2000-06-28; 260835 (Box 61, Folder 208)
    - Express Theatre Reception, 2000-06-29; 260836 (Box 61, Folder 209)
    - COGIC National AIM Convention, 2000-07-03; 260838 (Box 61, Folder 210)
    - Houston Firefighters Relief and Retirement Barbecue, 2000-07-07; 260839 (Box 61, Folder 211)
    - Clear Lake Area Economic Development Foundation, 2000-07-10; 260840 (Box 61, Folder 212)
    - Girl Scout Troop 5379, 2000-07-10; 260841 (Box 61, Folder 213)
    - National Association of Women in Construction, 2000-07-11; 260842 (Box 61, Folder 214)
    - Library Board Breakfast, 2000-07-12; 260843 (Box 61, Folder 215)
    - High Heat Awareness Press Conference, 2000-07-14; 260844 (Box 61, Folder 216)
    - International Association of Chiefs of Police, 2000-07-17; 260845 (Box 61, Folder 217)
    - Baptist Missionary Educational State Congress of Christian Education, 2000-07-18; 260846 (Box 61, Folder 218)
    - Census Party, 2000-07-18; 260847 (Box 61, Folder 219)
    - Ringling Brothers Circus New Ringmaster, 2000-07-18; 260848 (Box 61, Folder 220)
    - Independent Missionary Baptist General Association of Texas, 2000-07-19; 260849 (Box 61, Folder 221)
    - Executive Forum, 2000-07-20; 260850 (Box 61, Folder 222)
    - Houston Challenge 2000 Reception, 2000-07-20; 260851 (Box 61, Folder 223)
    - Department of Solid Waste Southeast Service Center Opening, 2000-07-21; 260852 (Box 61, Folder 224)
    - Census News Conference, 2000-07-24; 260853 (Box 61, Folder 225)
    - Houston Public Library - "City Leaders are Inventive Readers", 2000-07-24; 260854 (Box 61, Folder 226)
    - Career and Recovery Resources, Inc. Barrier Breaker Luncheon, 2000-07-25; 260855 (Box 61, Folder 227)
    - Patricia Cotton Recognition Ceremony, 2000-07-25; 260856 (Box 61, Folder 228)
    - Bishop McKinley Young Reception, 2000-07-26; 260857 (Box 61, Folder 229)
    - Housing Horizons - Humble Oil Building Groundbreaking, 2000-07-27; 260858 (Box 61, Folder 230)
    - Houston Bar Association All-Lawyer Musical Comedy Revue, 2000-07-28; 260859 (Box 61, Folder 231)
    - Making the Right Choices about Teenage Drinking, 2000-08-01; 260860 (Box 61, Folder 232)